Hello. Hello. How's it going? Sorry for keeping you in the meeting in the meeting in the waiting
room for too long. Listen back to back today. How are you guys doing? No problem. We're doing
good. Thank you. What about you? I am doing well. I don't think we've met. I'm Zaki. I run the AI
practice here. I'm just starting off like it's been a few days so very new at this but run the AI
practice at Sagan. Excited about having this call with you guys. I reviewed the original call. I
think that you guys had with John and Zach. With John? Yep. Yes. Perfect. And yeah, I'm just
jumping in and we were about to start your build. So I'd love to have any chance to get more context
before we start developing is always good. So I'm happy to meet you guys. Perfect. Great to meet
you too, Zaki. Thank you so much for taking the time to meet with us today. We really appreciate
it. Just a heads up, it's quite a complicated complex process. There are a lot of moving parts.
We were filling out the data point document for you. And we were just thinking literally we said,
I don't know how we're going to automate this. We're just going to trust your AI wizardry in
it because we have no clue on how that's going to work. But we do have a good starting point I
shared with you some documents with the templates basically on what we use. Did you walk through
it together? I'd love to get more context. I'm recording this too. So that'd be really good
input for it. Absolutely. Let me pull.
Just want to make sure I'm not. I want to use the ones that we've cleared client information from.
I put samples in our shared Dropbox today. Use those.
Yes, amazing. Fantastic.
In the onboarding materials folder.
Start with the SACS, which is like the first one we opened.
Okay. Let me move this because I can't see.
Okay. So I'm actually going to let Rebecca, if you're okay with it, Rebecca, to run through it.
Absolutely. Okay. So basically this is describing the way we like our clients to
have their banking. So we like them to have an inflow bank account, an outflow bank account,
and then a private reserve, which Marianne can scroll down a little bit. I can't, but there.
So the numbers in green at the top left, we will put the client's name and their salary,
like their actual dollars that come in after taxes because they'll make more and then taxes
come out. So those numbers are kind of set except for when they get a new job or maybe once a year
if they get a cost of living raise or something. So those don't change often. It's not a big deal
for us to manage those. And then the inflow number matches that. Everything that they make
goes into the inflow number, into the inflow number.
Inflow's coming in through right capital or precise FB, right? Those are the two tools we're using.
Inflow.
Like where does this data come in?
We are using those, but the inflow numbers should not change except again, yearly. Like
if their tax withdrawals change, if they get a raise, things like that. So that number should be
set. The little numbers at the bottom of the accounts that say $1,000 floor, that never
changes. We like them to have a $1,000 buffer in their accounts. So that number just stays the same.
Nice. Will you put us back on that screen, Marianne?
Yep. I was trying to have this other one next to it.
So I knew where the data was coming from, but I can't do it.
You're good. You're good. Okay. So then again, like this is hard for me to think of how we can
automate this at all because of the way we do it. But the red arrow with the X and it says
$12,000 a month, that number is based off of a budgeting worksheet that we give them.
So we know what a normal month of expenses and spending is. And then we take that and we plug
that in and we automate a transfer at their bank from their inflow to their outflow for
that amount every month. And then the blue arrow going down is simply the excess between the inflow
and outflow. So I guess it could be automated in the sense that we could just enter in the
info and it could be plugged in. Oh, yeah, absolutely. I think we could definitely do
this one pretty easily. In fact, we can make it pretty dynamic too, I think. It could account
for those changes, raises. That would be amazing because occasionally there's been an error when
we forget to change the number in the blue arrow or something like that. Okay, go to the second
page, please. So this one, usually the light blue says private reserve and that's basically
just their high yield savings account. And this one actually doesn't have the target on it,
but that's okay. Usually, Marianne, point to where the target is. Usually we input another
number there just in black and it's six months of their normal expenses based off that same
worksheet we used above and all of their insurance deductibles. So if they have a $1,000 car
deductible, $2,000 home deductible, $1,000 health deductible, we'll add all of that together
with six times their monthly expense and then that's their target for their savings.
So the number that says $75,000 right now, that is where we put in their balance.
And we get their balance on that account from their bank two days before the appointment
when we're creating the paperwork or the documents. The investment account,
that is usually from Schwab, Charles Schwab, and only two of us have authorization to go retrieve
that number because of security compliance. So myself or Andrew, our boss, we will go get that
number the day or two days before the appointment and then we have that number to put in. So that's
just their balance right there, the $15,000. So that is SACS. That's kind of the simpler one.
Interesting. Yeah, I'm just looking through the bills that we had. I think what you guys
already talked to John about, it's similar to that. I think you're all close. I do think that we could
make it like visually more appealing to the template here. I guess taking a step back,
would you want this to be like, is the vision here to generate like a final PDF one click
or to create a draft where we still have to do a little bit of work? Because Rebecca,
you log into Schwab as an agent to the customer, pull that data out. You could automate all of that
while respecting the rules, like the Schwab login is not a team login and all that good stuff.
What's the vision that we're sort of chasing? Like really good for you guys is the first step,
I guess. So I guess we should say that our boss Andrew created these documents and it took him
a very long time and he is happy with the way they look. So we're not looking to change the
appearance. This one actually is green. It's just the sample. It is in blue, our company colors.
But I don't think he is looking for a visual change, but Marianne take it away because I
was not involved in the start of this. So what? Well, if we could do a sample of what it could
look like without changing it too much, but just like, Hey, we're working with your format.
We love your format, but we're just sharing this for inspiration in case you want to use
any of these other like, I don't know. Yeah, I'm not even advocating for like a
visual changes. I'm just, I was just curious, like what you guys are hoping to do. Yeah.
Can you talk me through this screen? Cause this has got a lot more data coming in as
you know, from a bunch of different accounts and processes. So I'm, I do stuff on like on
your first page. Okay. Yeah. So first page. I guess top of my mind, both of them, we have
to manually input all the information. Everything. Yeah. So that would be a great
thing to move away from where maybe we have a list, you know, like a sidebar where we input
the information and it just automatically drops it into the PDF instead of us having to work with
the format and making sure that everything is aligned. And because that is a big thing on this,
if we move something, especially with the circle chart, this one gets moved and like the format
gets, I don't know. This one's in Canva. How often do you guys move things around here? Like
I build this thing in Canva and now I want to move this green bubble to the right and the
red bubble to the left, for example. We don't, we're not allowed to, we're not allowed to.
Okay. I did forget to tell you one thing where it says client example at the top.
You put the client's name and the date up there. So that's another thing we have to remember to
change every time. I'd love like you to send me like a PDF example of a final client, like with
the goal and the date and all that stuff. So we can like find, like we can align around that.
Do you like Canva more or do you like to do this in Word more? I can see a world
where we don't want to do it either. We want the form set so nothing can move. Because if you look
like where it says private reserve, the line is always off center. We just need it like set.
I like it. I'm going to, okay. I think I have an idea here. Like this could be,
this could be super interesting. And I like the idea of like we'll give you a little landing,
a little URL, a little app. It'll have like, hey, new report, right? And struggling to think
where we start from, like, and I want to like talk about that. Like where that client data,
how do you decide when to create a report for a client and where that client, like you would do
one for every customer that you have? So it depends on where the client is at on his process
with us. The ones that are already on, we have one that's on onboarding, for example,
the timeline of those meetings are going to change a little bit. But once they're settled with us,
and correct me if I'm wrong, Rebecca, but after like a year, they have quarterly meetings. And
there might be changes in that we might be meeting with them a little bit sooner or
on the later side. But once they're like, in depth with us, and we already have this system
down for them, then they're quarterly meetings every three months. You don't generate this
every month for them and send it to them by email. We do this for every client meeting.
So quarterly. But these numbers are monthly though, right? So this is like, hey,
here's what every month looks like. And then you make those transfers every month, of course.
Yes, because it's generally set, we build into their budget worksheet, we build in
a little excess, like any number they give us, we round up. Our clients are high net worth,
they're all millionaires. So they don't miss a few dollars here and there, you know.
So we round up in their budget every month. So this is extra, like whatever number is going to
their outflow, they don't have to be careful and watch every penny. So it stays the same generally,
and then any excess will be transferred out into their private reserve.
Cool. Yeah, I was just like, I mean, this is not for right now, but like for future,
like one thing we could do, since we're doing this, if we get this automated, you could just
send it to them by email every month, right? Here's what your numbers look like this month,
and you don't have to even wait for that three-monthly meeting to happen, right? Like,
just an idea. But let's try to get it to a point where it's like super easy to generate,
and then, you know, we can do more of it. Cool, very cool. Can we scroll down? I'm just curious
about the, well, or not scroll down, sorry, I meant the second report. I want to understand
each component or each box there. If you can make this slightly larger, that would be helpful too.
Yeah, yeah. All right.
That's your savings, time and accounts.
So let me walk you through this. So again, we have the name and date of the client in the
top left corner. And then those green bubbles, we have, they're usually, most of our clients are
married. So we have the spouses names, their age, their date of birth, the last four of
their social, and those don't really change other than the age. That would be nice to auto update
per year. Then in the upper left quadrant, I don't know where you are located.
So I don't know.
Austin.
Okay, great. So you are familiar with Mexico.
Marianne's in Mexican, but from, lives in France right now.
You guys win.
I'm American living in Mexico. She's Mexican living in France.
I'm Pakistani in Austin by way of Singapore in Montreal.
Wow.
I'd rather be in France and Mexico, but hey.
All right, cool. So retirement?
I don't know. I do love Austin. Homeslice Pizza is one of my favorite places.
So good. I used to live in California and that was, you know, from a, this report would make
me very nervous every month and I would get it from my accountant. It was like taxes would be
nightmare. So I like Austin a lot better now.
Okay. So I just wanted to know if you were like familiar with all the account types.
So you put this on the Roth IRA accounts, the 401Ks and their accounts, bank accounts,
basically.
So we put the last four of the account number where it says account number, we put the last four.
We put the type of account, we put the balance. And then I actually usually take the date off
because I think it looks messy, but we can leave the date if Andrew wants that.
And then the cash balance in that little bubble at the bottom.
Now the balance includes.
They're all the same date. We just moved that to a top right thing for
balance as of this date, or I guess some dates are different dates, I guess.
Well, and we have the date at the top left. So really, I take it off and he's never
complained. So I'm not, I don't care if that's on there or not.
But the balance, like, for example, on this Roth IRA in the top left, 11,162.47, that includes
the 316 cash. So basically the cash balance is there, but it's not, it's already added
into the balance. So it's not separate.
Yeah, it's your account of that, this investment in cash, right?
Yeah, it's telling you what's invested and what you have left in cash to invest.
Okay. So these accounts up here on the top half are retirement accounts. So it can only be
401ks, pensions, Roth IRAs, regular IRAs. That's all that can be up there.
And so for this quadrant on the upper left, for example, we have the IRA and the Roth IRA.
So this gray box at the top that says client one retirement only,
that is the total of these two accounts for the client.
Understood.
Go over to the other side, same thing. This one has three. So this gray box for client
to retirement only is these three numbers totaled. Then we go down and kind of in the center,
we have the trust. And usually the trust is funded by putting the client's house into the
trust. So this number is actually updated every meeting. We go look up the value of their house
from Zillow, which I know it's not accurate, but it's a good measure of if the market's going up
or down. Yeah. The exact dollar amount doesn't really matter in terms of the zestimate, right?
You pull the zestimate.
Yes. We go to Zillow, we type in their address and it just pops up the zestimate. So that's
actually where that number comes from. Super scientific, I know.
If you want to make zestimate minus 5%, then it's best to be profitable.
Exactly. It goes up and down, but we always know, has the market gone up since your last
appointment or has the market gone down? It would be different if a realtor came and assessed.
Yeah, they're giving me a snapshot of my net worth. Honestly, every account goes up and down.
Every trading account goes up and down pretty rapidly too, probably more than your house,
to be honest with you, every month.
Oh, for sure. I mean, sometimes in a day we see our clients' accounts go up or down
like $100,000.
Actually, 2026, right? Yeah, don't get me sorry about that. It's crazy out there.
Cool. And so there's two kinds of accounts. Sorry, I just want to make sure I understand.
There's two kinds of accounts essentially. There's bank accounts, which are cash essentially,
and there's various kinds of bank accounts, right? There's retirement bank accounts,
and there's savings accounts, and checking accounts, all that good stuff.
And then there's joint accounts, all that stuff too. We haven't talked about joint
accounts in here. I always see it separate out with client one, client two. How do you
represent joint accounts would be a question I have, if that exists at all? Or is it always
the same? And then these are all the bubbles available. We decide what bubbles they actually
have, what kind of accounts they have. We drop those in. That would be an option.
Let's start there. Let's talk about that. Are there any?
Yes. So we personalize this for every client. We make however many bubbles we need.
So on the bottom, where it says non-retirement, on the right here, we... Okay. Also, I should say,
in most of our client situations, there is a high earning spouse and a low or no earning spouse.
So it's very easy to just put the overflow into that. But usually, their bank accounts are on
the bottom right. These are joint accounts. These are the accounts that are on the SACS,
the inflow, the outflow, and the private reserve. So those are still there. Now,
if there's no space on that side, we would move them to the other side. It doesn't matter on the
bottom. Most of these are joint accounts. I was telling Marianne earlier, for example,
if I had a Schwab brokerage account, I could have that with my husband and we both can contribute.
But the retirement accounts, like you probably have for your job, it's only for you. It's
not for a spouse. So the ones on the bottom can be mixed. The ones on the top cannot be mixed.
Right. And I could have non-retirement accounts that are solo too, though, right?
Yes. And we put those on here. And if the client does have it, we put it on their side.
Just put on their side in non-retirement, basically, right?
Yeah. For example, we have one client who gets stock options. And so on her side,
she's got a little E-Trade account that her husband doesn't have. But it doesn't matter, really.
But it's not retirement, really. It's options. Cool. Sounds good. And then new value of options,
too. I'm curious about that. Is that public stock options? Where do you bring a number
in for the value of the... I guess it's a public company. It's not a public company.
Oh, we only update that once a year when she gets her...
A valuation, a 4 or 9A valuation.
Yeah. So just one time a year. And then the rest of the year, it'll have this little red
asterisk that says it's not up to date.
Well, I'm learning. I'm not working my accountant hard enough is what I'm learning
in this course. I have one more of these myself. That'd be great.
We can help you with that.
Okay. So yeah, any non-retirement accounts, any other investments that are not retirement,
anything else is added there on the bottom. And then when we go to add,
we go to add these up, we do not add the trust in. Okay. So the non-retirement total right here,
the gray bottom. This is only the accounts, not the trust.
Gotcha. Okay.
Then we'll go to liabilities. So liabilities are any debts that they have, car loans, mortgage,
usually nobody, none of our clients have other debts other than those.
So we like to have, and this one's missing the interest rate.
We do like to have what it is. So like mortgage, whatever, mortgage, auto, we like to have the
interest rate in a column in the middle between these, we have the balance. And then with all
the different liabilities that we have, we total the liabilities up here at the top in that light
gray box. Oh, here. Oh yeah. Sorry. I'm like doing it with my mouse, but you're doing it with yours.
Okay. Nice liabilities on top is this little box is just the total of anything on the bottom.
So sometimes there's nothing, sometimes it's one thing, it depends, but we total the liabilities.
Then may I add all of that math is done manually. So even just automating that
would be great. Yeah, because there's errors and we have to keep double checking and things like that.
So now we have done all of the work on this chart. So we take these, we take all the gray boxes. So we
take the client one retirement, we take the client two retirement, the non-retirement total,
and the trust. This is where the trust comes in. So we add the three boxes plus the trust,
and that is the grand total of their net worth. So your time in one retirement to total retirement,
a non-retirement, and then trust is grand total. Those four numbers go into that and then you might,
and the liabilities are underneath that. The liabilities are separate. We do not subtract
liabilities from their net worth. They're just a separate box. So their net worth is client one
retirement, client two retirement, non-retirement, trust, and then liabilities are separate underneath.
So that's how we come to all the numbers. Cool. Amazing. And we detailed that for you in a
document so you can go back to it. Yeah. Okay, let's talk about where we get the numbers. Yes,
yes, yes, that's exactly right. Okay. So this part is also tricky. Oh, we didn't show him the
monthly expense. That's the only one we were missing, just so he knows from this for the SACS.
So for SACS, the information we pull from here are agreed on amounts from their monthly expense
worksheet, which looks like this. They fill it out. You mean the outflow, right? The expenses
outflow and that. Yes, yes, expenses outflow. Exactly. Like the stuff that's going into
like the non-private reserve stuff. What they earn, how much they need, what's going to be
transferred, what goes to the private reserve. Understood. That makes a lot of sense.
Perfect. So we'll go through that. But when you say monthly agreed upon amount, that's like
that, the guy that's been moving, you have them fill out a sheet of expenses sheet when their
intake, when they're getting onboarded, I assume. Yeah. And then you just transfer what
the expenses are to the red account. Yeah. So let's say their regular monthly bills were like
$15,000. We would round up and they probably would be transferring like $18,000 every month
to the outflow. So there's a buffer. So their inflow is like 40 grand and everything remainder
goes down to like the private reserve and then gets divided up based on whatever you have.
We want them to live in like a mental state of abundance. So they're never like,
oh my gosh, do I have enough money in my account to go out to dinner?
So that's why we round it up. And then just periodically when they do, like we call it
an audit at the end of the month, it takes like 15 minutes. They just account for what they
spent and the actual numbers. Then they can transfer any excess they did not spend out into
the private reserve as well. Do you send them the sheet in advance or after the fact? Is it
the end of the month or the start of the month? They do the audit at the end of the month and we
actually never see the audit. That's just something they do on their own. What I mean to say is that
they get the expenses sheet after the audit is done and they move that amount into the private
reserve. So we give them the monthly expensive sheet when they first start and then we just
adjust as necessary. So if we're in the quarterly update, that goes out at the end
of the quarter before. And so basically what I mean to say is the stuff that they do to like,
you know, they fill out their sheet. They go like, guys, they have three grand on my expenses.
I can move that into private reserve. That's after the sheet has gone out, right? Like that's,
does that make sense? Yes, it makes sense. I understand now. No. So we prepare this,
but we have access to their bank balance. Right. So we just update it without ever
talking about it unless they need to talk about it. Because if they're like under budget and
transferring excess, we don't really talk about it. If they're overspending and they keep
transferring excess into their outflow, then we talk about it and revisit it. But otherwise,
once they get it set, they're, they're all kind of just, they're just normal people. Like they
don't spend excessively usually. Um, so we don't revisit it often, if that makes sense.
Very nice. We show them. Yeah. And this is a snapshot of a moment in time, basically. Right.
So like, if you generate the report today, it's, I think that's the case before. Yeah.
Right. Um, I'd love to understand where the data is coming from.
Okay. Okay. We're back. So we can start with Saks. Is that okay? Or would you like me to
zoom in? No, no, start here. This is great. I'd love to see like, especially the site. Yeah.
Perfect. Um, so all credit to Rebecca, because she was the one that helped me put this together.
But the inflow, like we said, we pull a client salary and we gather this info from our,
when we onboard them, if it changes, where do you find this? Sorry, I'm cutting off.
Let's say I'm preparing a report like six months after onboarding has ended and you have a new
person coming in, where would they find what the agreed upon inflow was essentially?
Is there like a record? Is there like a record somewhere of customers, like a CRM,
like a, like an air table or something? It's on that. It's on that Excel spreadsheet. Yeah.
I see. Okay. That budgeting spreadsheet that they fill out and we help them round up. We
just have a copy of that. And it's actually an Excel sheet, not a Google sheet, not in the,
I'm trying to figure out, can I read this? Like, can, can my, can my, can the AI agent
we build for you guys just go read that automatically and save you the step of
entering? Like, you know, does that make sense? Well, we can submit the monthly,
the Excel spreadsheet. We don't have this recorded somewhere internally in a system that, hey,
client one and client two. Nope, not yet. Okay. Oh yeah. Yeah. Not yet.
We're a very small operation. There's three of us. Yeah. That's why you need more agents.
So we're happy to be helping you guys. We can help customers without adding too many more
people. I'm curious, like how many time, how many customers have you guys got that you're
sending this out for? So our fees are, our fees are very high and we don't need that many clients.
If that makes sense, we have about six, like regular, they pay us monthly. And then we have
assets under management, you know, all assets, all, all retirement investment plans charge a fee.
And so we have, we have income from that as well. So it's important. Like, I mean, we're not doing
this process so many times every month that you can really put eyeballs on it, basically. And like,
really like get it right, essentially, right? Like that's what we can, but you know, Marianne
is like a wonderful, wonderful assistant. But before her, we went through three in
like the first five months that I worked here. And then we didn't have an assistant
for three months before we got her. So it was like, I was doing my job and her job. And
and then for that with the other assistants, it was just like mistake after mistake after mistake.
And you know, so Marianne's doing great, but it would be nice for everybody to automate it
and have a more. Yeah, yeah. If we can take this takes us a day to prepare, if we could take this
down to an hour, where we don't have to manually do the math where some of these might not be AI.
I worked temporarily for a like Google advertising company. And they had the reports that they
shared with the clients on a monthly basis. And I think it was done through Google data,
something like that. It was a Google software. And basically, we had a studio. Sorry,
Data Studio, Google Data Studio, Data Studio. Yes. Something like that would be great. I mean,
there are some things that are not going to be updated automatically. And that we know that have
to be input manually. That's okay. But if the format, it lives in a place where it doesn't get
messed up if we input. It's just like a preset format. That would be great. If it does the math
for us, that would be fantastic. And then the things that we can automate, then that would
be of a great plus, too. Yeah. Well, and I just want to say for compliance, we cannot use anything
Google will have to be something secure. Even AI is actually really tricky because
I can speak to that. And let's hold that thought till the end of this call, because I fully
understand. But then at the same time, there's the way we use AI stores, nothing for training,
to use like regular commercial AI, everything you put in there is then used for training the next
version. But we don't do that. And so that's great. But yeah, I'm imagining a role where we build you
I'm sorry, I'm painting a picture, but I tried to stay up solutions. But I want to make sure we get
this just right for you guys. And so we dial it in. I'm imagining a world where we build you a
simple portal, right? Where you're able to set up a new customer. And like you have six at the
moment, that might be 12 next year, right? And we want to be able to get you there without adding
more employees. And that's the beauty of AI and agents especially. So you set up a customer, you
fill up a few fields, and these are fields that don't change very often, your inflow, your
outflow, your inflow, your outflow, you know, stuff that's static, not bad. And maybe you
add like, Hey, here's all the accounts associated with them. And when I say add accounts, I mean,
just give me the last four digits or whatever, right? Or like, Hey, Wells Fargo account number.
And if you have like any keys, I'm not saying passwords, keys that allow us to log in
automatically. What we can then do is we can every month, or when you hit a button saying
generate new reports, it would go pick up your customer list, you know, figure out the
stuff that's static is easy pulls that out of that of that CRM that we built a very simple,
like, this will be an Excel spreadsheet, it won't look anything complicated with like a bunch
of columns, pulls that out, pulls out details about the bank accounts that we need to pull
information from, right? Because everyone has a different number of accounts. And I imagine
there'll be like types there, they'll be like, this is a checking account, checking or savings,
this is an investment account. So then we know, hey, this guy can have like an investment account
amount, and we got to pull the cash amount too, versus this guy's just cash, right? And this
other guy is like something else entirely. So we could have, I see people who have accounts,
I see bank accounts, and I see investment accounts, right? And that's basically the
two types we have, the third I'd love to know, pulls that information and automatically,
right? So that stuff is automated as much as possible, when it can, sometimes it won't be
able to pull it automatically. So like, sometimes, like, for when you have like the,
the investment accounts, the shop accounts, right? And so it won't pull it automatically.
But then that's a decision you guys make, right? Like, if you see us,
in version one of this is able to handle basic accounting information and pulling in
automatically, then version two, our next edit on this could be, hey, pull that into
automatically, right? And that we can do in a very secure way, using your credentials,
Rebecca, without giving access to anybody else, right? Only the agent have access with you. And
that's better, more trust, it's easier to trust than like, and that can be read only access to.
So that doesn't have to be right access to those accounts. And then we can set them up
in the tokens correctly, too. So we can go next step and pull all of them, but it'll try to pull
as much information as it can, in the account sheet, right? The next other sheet you showed me,
and create like, draft one of this sheet, but not quite yet fully, it will say, hey,
I don't have these four things, or these six things. And so can you pull those in manually?
And then once you pull those, put those amounts in, click generate, it will create a PDF for you.
Maybe it creates it for you in Canva as well. So you can also move bubbles around,
you need to make some edits, right? Like with PDF. That sounds great.
So I'm just thinking in right capital, which is where we get a lot of our information from
the other one, the one with all the little circles. Right, capital is really tricky because
it's not always up to date. So when I look on to write capital, we have to go refresh,
like let it re-sync all the client's accounts. And then sometimes, most of the time, there are
still several accounts that aren't linked. And so then I have to look at that exact account,
and I'm like, where is this account located? How do I get an updated number? So sometimes
I'll have to go ask the client for a statement. Sometimes I'll have to log into a separate website
if I have access to whatever. What it can do is it will first try to like fiddle around with
write capital's API to make sure it's updating that information. Sometimes you can, I haven't
looked at the API too deeply, but you have to push it to update, and then it updates,
and then you can pull that in. But it will still have certain fields that are missing.
I'll flag those. And you can't generate a full report till it does that. It could create a drop
for you if you really want to see it. But what it'll ask you is, hey, I bought these six numbers,
I need these four. For these accounts that are set up in the CRM, you still need to find me
numbers. So maybe we could manually override also and just say like, use the old number.
Because write capital will have numbers from like six months ago or a year ago or whatever.
You could give it some obviously good one, like use the last number, you can have a little button
on it. And then by the way, those buttons are real time. So like you could click that button
and see what it pulls in. Or you could say that number looks wrong. I'm going to find this out the
other way, right? Manual override where it's put a number and you're like, nah, I want to add
this number instead. So like, you still get, Marianne, you still have to like do a review
of the draft, right? Yeah. You don't have to build from scratch. And then all the internal
rules like this minus this is equal to private reserve and that goes, that's just baked into
the, you don't have to think about that, right? Yeah. So you're only focusing on the things
that only you can do essentially. The idea of it living in a portal.
The idea of it living in a portal work, because right now we use Canva, we use Word, we use the
monthly spreadsheet, but it's all, it all lives in different places. And to me, that is very
stressful. We can go to one place, one portal where we have this live. And it just, we work
on all of like the circle chart and the sacks on the same spot. And it's being stored because
also a big portion of it is where is it being stored? Can we have it drop it into their Dropbox
automatically linked to Dropbox and it's being stored proactively instead of us having to
look around for files all the time. That just, that portion alone sounds great,
having everything in one spot, being able to work on both of them in one same spot, same format.
And then even if we can add like this, just like a little SOP that we can refer to directly on that
portal, that would be fantastic. If anyone else would be super helpful. What about the monthly
expense worksheet? If we're dreaming big here, couldn't that be a piece of the portal where
the clients can only access that, but that's a link we can send out rather than an Excel file
that we're going to have to update. I think what we should do is, I mean, sorry, sorry. We should
pick out one problem and let's take a step back. Here's what I'm very good at.
You can't solve everything at once.
No, we can. We absolutely can. And I like how John explains it. It's,
it's, you know, we're building Lego city, but we've got to find one brick at a time, right?
Yeah, I love that.
But what I'm loving about this is I think we build you decline portal. And that seems to be
like there's a bigger, there's a problem of repetitive doing things repeatedly. But like,
I think what you said, Marianne, about like, there's no central place for a client to kick,
you don't have to keep things off from or store data, like basic onboarding data.
If you can just build you that and then yeah, right now we could just input that manually
to the portal one time, because some of these things are one time. And then use this for
like solving that generation. Our goal is to build you the portal, but really the goal is to
like solve the problem we solve with like generating PDFs of their monthly reports,
basically quarter.
And I know that that is something that Andrew wants. He wants.
But we can bring that same, we can come back to it and say, now, what else can we do of
this portal? And oh, we can build you agent number two, and this is your onboarding agent.
So you go like, I don't want to enter stuff manually into this guy. Here's an email address,
send them our onboarding form and let them fill it out. And it can be really interactive.
You can send them reminders automatically. And then ping you guys only when we've
sent them like four reminders and they haven't done anything for like a week, right?
And then you're like, Hey, you guys should pull it. Yeah, have Andrew call them, right?
And so I think that's the beauty of it. Like we can build you like it's like instead of
promising you everything on day one, I want to really focus on something that can solve a really
big problem or a big enough problem for you guys, because only $500. Also,
like we charge you a credit to build this. So it's like, we scope it down to like a very
small, narrow problem. And then we can add more to it, right? Agent two, and I'm sure you'll need
revisions on this too. You're going to come to me and go like, Hey, can you pull all this information
directly instead of having us enter stuff? And that can be like a direction we take it in.
Or can you like also do onboarding or can you do both? So it's really important that we show you
guys the power of these agents with one very specked out thing. I think I have a really good
example here that we can help with. But then it's really good to think about what else can
we help with. And I think that comes down the pike, right? Once you guys are really seeing the value
and what we built you over here. Yeah. Yeah. We're the only software company is going to be like, Hey,
don't buy more software from us. Stick to one thing and then we'll stop there and then we'll go.
Okay. Like when you say let's build a client portal, is this a website?
Well, yeah, it'll be a web app. Like it'll be an app, you log into it, it'll be like,
and you know, we hope and, and we have to pay for hosting for that. Nope. Nope. You don't
pay for hosting as good question. So as long as you're a member of Sagan, which is, you know,
what we really want you to be the monthly. Yes. We charge you a flat fee to build it.
And so after this call, I'm going to like create a spec, right? And send you a spec over email
and say, Hey, Rebecca and Marianne, here's what we spoke about. Here's what we're going to
build for you. Here's a one-liner and here's like three bullets on what it's going to do,
right? Covering the, and then you give it a thumbs up and you say, yeah, build it. We
burn one credit from your plan, which is like $500 or you can just pay for it if you want to
keep the credit. I think we, we still have like two credits, I think. Yeah. Some folks tend to want
to like, Hey, I'm hiring to build this here. So I'll just keep the credits, but I want to
burn. Like, uh, I'll just give you guys money. So read your call, but you can do it when I
credit and we'll go build it for you. And that's flat. It's one time. It's not like
a monthly fee or anything, right? And we'll host the app for you. We'll host the infrastructure. We'll
host, we'll even monitor up time, make sure it's still working. You know, it won't have bugs in
it and stuff. Um, and you only pay for usage from that point onwards. What that means is we're
charging you every time you use it for like the data and the tokens you're using, the AI using
inside it, we charge the cost plus 20%. So like it's flat, you know, you're paying tens of
dollars a month, not hundreds of dollars a month and you're getting really custom software at
scale. So perfect. And that's where the Lego bricks come in, right? We've got to scope it down to
something very manageable and then we can launch that and then do more of those essentially. All
right. I want to hear about the incoming, like, so we've got, uh, the data that's incoming here.
We've got bank accounts and they're coming in through, do you see the right capital? Is that
the company? So bank accounts, we usually get through Pinnacle bank and we request that by
email a couple of days before the meeting, their personal bankers, their personal bankers for our
clients. So you actually ask all your customers to sign up for like Pinnacle bank as a, as a, as a,
yes. And we work very closely with the bankers. So at any point we have access to request
all of their balances or like their statement history or anything like that. Very cool. Um,
does that, is that an email you send out manually? And they send us a secure email
that we have to log on. Yeah. Okay. We'll have to, where I see challenges here will be
like getting some of this, it'll be easy to fetch, right? And then some of it is going to be a little
bit harder to fetch the stuff. That's like one time easy to fetch. You import that one time.
It's like we pulled that in, um, all the bank and then Schwab is like, and you mentioned Schwab,
which is basically Andrew and Rebecca log in as authorized users and pull that data. And those
are the only two kinds of accounts you have, like by account of Pinnacle or right. Capital
is an overview of like they could have their liabilities on there. Like their, their car
loans, their mortgages, they can link their investment accounts that are outside of Schwab.
Schwab are the ones we meet, but they, you know, some have fidelity or Edward Jones or whatever
from previous jobs. I imagine right. Capital kind of gives us a little peek, but right
capital, that login for sure cannot be shared with any, um, agent because it's not even my
login or Andrews. It belongs to somebody Andrew used to work with. Um, and we have access to
that program through him, but I don't think it's a big deal if we built the agent to say,
enter in the Schwab info, enter in the Pinnacle info, enter in the right capital,
and then I'm going to place it in the right thing, the right spot.
Because I don't think we can give it access to any of these, any of those three things.
I mean, I know that right capital has an API so you might not, I mean, but, but there's
two complexities here, right? It's like, Hey, how do you give it access? And then how do you
get past the fact that it's not your account, which might be the bigger prayer barrier. Um,
I would say not to trust right capital that much just because their own API, like how they
connect the other accounts is not perfect. Um, like we've seen it struggle a lot and it's not
synced. Um, they have like delays and information, or there are some accounts that cannot be plugged
in to write capital just because you can make that second version. Yeah. If you make that a second
version, we go like, um, yeah, I can see as, I can see us finding ways to minimize that. And maybe
we just build you something and move your customers off, right? Capital, if that's all they're
hosting in their legacy, because all the connections are coming in through like Plaid,
right? Or one of those like third party tools. So they're not building each of these connections
and separately, you could just connect you into Plaid and then have you, but then I think that
might be the next one or the one after that that we do for you. What is precise FP? I see that
you have that mentioned in your original meeting too. Um, we use precise FP. So, uh, they do like
their crop client profile there. They have their age of birth, uh, their date of birth. They have,
um, a listed family, for example. Um, it's just, we send them a questionnaire through precise FP
that they fill out during like different stages of the onboarding. So the advisors that they work
with are also there. Um, it's just, I would say the closest thing we have to a CRM where
all of the data for each client is stored in. Interesting. Okay. But we don't, since we have
six customers, I feel like clients, we should probably upload them in one time directly. We
don't have to like build like a, like a hook into, do you see any reason to build a hook into
precise FP? No, no, no, no, no, no. I think we can manually input the information one by one.
Okay. I think I have a good sense and feel for version one. I'll just like say it back to you
guys. And then you can like, um, tell me if I have a good sense of it. I think we need to build you
guys. Uh, okay. There was a key constraint you had laid out in the previous build, which was like
zero manual data entry, which Andrew and Zach, Andrew and John and Zach had talked about.
I think we get to that constraint because like there's going to be some data entry over here
and I have a good sense and it's always good to talk to the folks that actually do the work
and that's the big one. And so I think everything else we talked about works makes sense. We're
going to build you a system where you can insert clients, right? One time like that can come up
precise FP, or you can just add them in manually. It doesn't matter. Um, that's your intake
information, including accounts that they link, all the accounts that they have, right? So you'll
be able to add link, like just the information that we need to create the PDF. And then we're
going to give you the ability to click, like create a new report, right? And that report,
since it doesn't have to be like, you can just click a button for it to generate a new report.
Try to pull in as much information as it can, right? Now it'll pull in stuff from onboarding.
It'll pull in stuff from, um, like whatever it has access to, but it doesn't have access to
any live data on like reporting on numbers. So, but it can, and correct me if I'm wrong,
right? Like if I, because the background details are coming from, right,
which we can't trust and don't have access to directly. And then there's like,
so what we need to do is consolidate all the stuff that needs to go into it
and give you a little checklist. So it goes like, Hey, enter everything in here,
right? And then once you're done with that, you hit generate and that creates a report
with all the rules that you talked about, looks better, lines are aligned. Look, you know,
we can make it, we can make it exactly the same, but like make it look a little bit more
polished and like, you know, get it to like, I like that, I like that a little revamp.
I think we won't change the format at all. We'll just change the user experience and then the user
interface. Basically is how we talk about it in software and give a little paint job and boom,
ready to go. And then you have that in Canva as a draft so that you can change, make visual
changes to it if you need to, or you can download as a PDF right there, both from the same
interface. You can export to Canva or download as PDF. You get choices and perfect. Oh, okay.
Perfect. Yeah. I think that's good. It won't save the report. You can just download it
or you can send it to Canva and Canva will save it for you. Right. So that way you it's, it's,
it's more robust. And then we have future directions. We have two future directions
we talked about. We can bring that data in automatically and we can talk about that.
Like there's, there's definitely ways to like, and then we can like help you with
onboarding maybe. Right. Yeah. That could be interesting too. Okay. Other
options for us to help as well. So that could be agents two, three, and four. Like
I think of agents as like, as you know, people don't think it's employees and they're not
really employees. They're like an employee is a collection of agents. Right. And so you do five
things. One of those things is an agent or maybe half of that one thing is an agent. So like,
start thinking like that and then we can like help you guys. Cause like, this is a great
challenge. Like as your lean team and you have high net worth individuals, which means
expectations are higher and you want to grow without expanding the team too much. Right. So
this is like our sweet spot for sure. Okay. Great. Well, we'll look up, we'll look out for your
brief on what you said you would send and then I'll probably connect with Andrew just to walk
through everything and what we agreed on and get back to you with next steps probably by the end
of the week or give me a, I will send you guys a, by tomorrow I'll send you a bill spec. It'll be
like a one-liner. Here's what we're going to build for you and like three or four bullets.
And here's what we're going to do specifically. Right. You'll have to just reply back and give
me a thumbs up saying, Hey, build it. That's the point where we burn the credit and start
a development process for you. And we can show prototype to you within a week after that. So
like, yes, please discuss this with Andrew internally and then give us a thumbs up on
that email and we'll start to build and we'll send you a prototype very quickly after that.
Sounds great. Thank you so much. Thank you so much. Thank you. Very nice to meet you.
Good to meet you guys too and hope to work with you guys for a while.
If you have any other questions, just email us.
Thank you. Cheers. Bye. Bye.